slimwareutilities.com 2016-10-20

# SlimWare Utilities - Privacy Policy

**NOTICE** : _Last Updated July 9th, 2015_

Slimware Utilities Holdings, Inc. (collectively, " **Slimware Utilities** ", " **we** ", " **us** " or " **our** ") has developed this privacy policy to demonstrate its commitment to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") is intended to describe for you, as an individual who is a user of the Slimware Utilities websites, mobile apps, social media sites, software and/or services (collectively the "Services"), the information we collect, how that information may be used, with whom it may be shared, and your choices about such uses and disclosures. We seek to handle the information we collect in a manner that complies fully with the privacy requirements under all applicable United States federal and state privacy laws and regulations. 

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully. By using the Services, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy, and agreeing to the processing and storage of information we collect from you in the United States and, in connection with certain Services, the Philippines and other non-United States jurisdictions. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions set forth in this Privacy Policy, then please do not provide us with any information and do not access, browse or use the Services. If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us. 

## INFORMATION WE COLLECT

The information we collect will either be 1) Personal Information or 2) Anonymous Information. __Personal Information__ means information that may directly or indirectly identify you, such as your name, address, email address, and telephone number. __Anonymous Information__ means information that does not directly or indirectly identify you, such as the number of page views, link clicks, and login times. We may use both Personal and Anonymous Information to create Aggregate Information. __Aggregate Information__ is derived from the grouping of information we collect into groups and/or categories, which does not identify you directly or indirectly. 

Through your use of the Services, we (or our service providers on our behalf) may collect the following information as Personal Information, Anonymous Information or Aggregate Information: 

  * Contact information and/or registration information, such as your name; and business and residential mailing address, telephone and facsimile numbers and email address; 
  * information you provided in posting areas, public forums, social networks, and surveys; 
  * Information you provided us while using the Services, including files that you uploaded, and the use of the Services on third-party sites or platforms such as social networking sites; 
  * Purchase information, including credit card or payment card information and billing address; 
  * Demographic information, including age, personal interests, and product preferences; 
  * Information regarding your use of the Services, such as browsing, downloads and pages viewed; 
  * Technical data, associated with any computer or other device you use to access the services, or software therein such as the software and settings on your device and your device identifier or IP address; 
  * Such other information we collect with your consent or as permitted or required by law. 

## HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION

We (or our service providers on our behalf) use various methods and technologies to collect information from you, and about your computer or device (or software thereon) and about your activities on or through the Services: 

  * **Submitted information.** We will collect information you voluntarily provide or submit. 
  * **Automatically Captured Information.** We may automatically collect information from your computer and/or device (or software thereon) when you use the Services. This information may include your IP address, your browser type and language, access times, current installed applications, system registry settings, driver versions, system start up settings, and the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us (see "Cookies" below), and the referring website address. 
  * **Cookies.** When you use the Services, we may assign your computer one or more cookies, to facilitate access to our Services and to personalize your online experience. A cookie is a small piece of data that is stored in a user's computer for record keeping purposes. Our Services may us HTTP cookies, HTML5 cookies, Flash cookies and other types of local storage (such as browser-based or plugin-based local storage). Through the use of a cookie, we may automatically collect information about your activity on our Services, such as the actions you take within the Services, and the application and/or updates you have installed onto your computer or device. Most systems automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, please note that you may not be able to sign in or use some of the interactive features offered on or via the Services. Your browser may tell you how to be notified when you receive certain types of cookies and how to restrict or disable certain cookies. To learn more about some types of browser cookies, visit allaboutcookies.org. You also may be able to delete your Flash cookies or adjust your Flash cookie settings by visiting the Adobe Flash Website Storage Settings Manager by following Adobe.s instructions here (instructions vary depending on your operating system and version of Flash). Please note, however, that without cookies or local storage you may not be able to use all of the features of our Service. 
  * **Other Technologies.** We may use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons and Flash cookies and other similar technologies, to track your use of the Services. Web beacons are small pieces of data that are embed in images on the pages of sites. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the Services. 
  * **Do Not Track.** We do not respond to the Do Not Track browser setting. 

## INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THIRD PARTIES FOR ON-LINE ADVERTISING

We may allow third-parties, including our authorized service providers, parent and subsidiary companies, affiliates, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements or place ad tags or beacons on or via our Services on the computer or device you use to access our Service and to track that device to over time and across different web sites for the purpose of serving advertising relevant to your interests. We do not control third parties. collection or use of information to serve interest based advertising. Some but not all providers may allow you to opt-out of receiving their targeted ads, see <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>. 

## HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We may use information that we collect about you to:

  * Identify, establish and maintain our relationship with you; 
  * Deliver Services and information that you have requested and otherwise allow you to fully participate in the interactive features of our Services; 
  * Notify you about your account, including expiration and renewal notices; 
  * Provide you with customer support; 
  * Perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services, or content, or products, services or content offered by others; 
  * Communicate with you by e-mail, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us, our parent or subsidiary companies or other third parties; 
  * Process, validate and verify purchases; 
  * Register you as a customer; 
  * Enforce our terms and conditions and notify you of changes to our Services; 
  * Manage and improve our business; 
  * Meet legal regulatory, insurance security and processing requirements and court or administrative orders or as required by law; 
  * Maintain business records for reasonable periods; and 
  * Perform any other functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection and any other purpose with your consent. 
  * **Authorized service providers:** We may share your Personal Information with our authorized service providers that perform services on our behalf. These services may include, for example, providing customer service and marketing assistance, delivering advertising, performing business and sales analysis, supporting our Services. functionality, delivering Services on our behalf, and supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys and other features offered through our Services. These service providers may have access to Personal Information, which is needed to perform their functions, but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes. 
  * **Third-party businesses:** We may sell, share or rent your Personal Information with businesses to offer you their products, services, promotions, contests and/or sweepstakes. When you elect to engage in a particular merchant's offer or program, you authorize us to provide your email address and other information to that merchant. 
  * **Other IAC businesses.** We are part of the IAC family of businesses ([www.iac.com](http://www.iac.com/)). We may share information we collect, including Personal Information, with our IAC companies. Sharing information with our IAC family companies enables us to provide you with information about a variety of products and services that might interest you. 
  * **Other Situations.** We or our authorized service provider(s) may disclose your Personal Information (i) in response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency, (ii) in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; (iii) to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; (iv) to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement; (v) to enforce our Services. terms and conditions or other agreements or policies; and (vi) in connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business or the Services, a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy in which event we may assign or otherwise transfer all our rights in such data without restriction. 

## THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES

There may be places in the Services where you may click on a link to access other websites that do not operate under this Privacy Policy. For example, if you click on a link, you may be taken to a website that we do not control. These third-party websites may independently solicit and collect information, including Personal Information, from you and, in some instances, provide us with information about your activities on those websites. We recommend that you consult the privacy policy of all third-party websites you visit. 

## YOUR CHOICES ABOUT COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR INFORMATION

You may tell us not to share your Personal Information with third parties or the IAC companies for direct marketing purposes by clicking on the following link and entering the email address associated with your account: [info@slimwareutilities.com](mailto:info@slimwareutilities.com). Please note, if you do not allow us to collect Personal Information from you, it may result in you being unable to use certain features of the Services; purchase products or services; participate in a contest, promotion, survey, or sweepstakes; ask a question; or initiate other transactions on our Services. 

Some but not all providers may allow you to opt-out of receiving their targeted ads, see <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>. 

As stated above, your browser may tell you how to be notified when you receive certain types of cookies and how to restrict or disable certain cookies. To learn more about some types of browser cookies, visit allaboutcookies.org. You also may be able to delete your Flash cookies or adjust your Flash cookie settings by visiting the Adobe Flash Website Storage Settings Manager by following Adobe.s instructions here (instructions vary depending on your operating system and version of Flash). Please note, however, that without cookies or local storage you may not be able to use all of the features of our Service. 

## HOW WE PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

The security and confidentiality of you information is very important to us; thus we have put in place administrative, technical, and physical safeguards to protect against unauthorized access to the information we collect. By using the Services and accepting this Privacy Policy, you hereby acknowledge that no security system is immune from compromise, and you accept all responsibility for such security risks and any damage resulting therefrom. 

## CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

Our Services are intended for general audiences over the age of 13 years old. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13 years old. If you are not over 13 years old, **__DO NOT DOWNLOAD OR USE THE SERVICES__**. 

## USING OUR SERVICES FROM OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES

If you are using the Services outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. In connection with certain Services, your information may also be transferred to, stored, and processed in other jurisdictions outside of the United States. By using our Services, you hereby agree to the transfer, storage and processing of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

## NO RIGHTSOF THIRD PARTIES

This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties and no third party is an intended beneficiary of this Privacy Policy. 

## CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. We will provide you notice of these changes by posting changes to this Privacy Policy. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "Last Updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy, and your continued use of the Services constitute consent to the revised Privacy Policy. If we make any changes that we determine, in the reasonable exercise of our discretion, will reduce your rights under the Privacy Policy, we will provide a more prominent notice (including for certain services email notification of Privacy Policy changes). We will obtain your affirmative consent for retroactive changes to your rights to the extent required by applicable law. 

## CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE

It is our policy to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act, which permits our customers who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to the address listed below. 

## BINDING ARBITRATION AND CLASS ACTION WAIVER

This Policy shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of New York without regard to the conflicts of law provisions thereof. You expressly agree that any controversy, dispute or claim (.Litigation.) arising out of, relating to, or in connection with, this Privacy Policy or the Services, or the alleged breach thereof, or relating to our activities or services or to us otherwise under this Privacy Policy, shall be settled by confidential binding arbitration in New York County, New York, in accordance with the applicable rules of the American Arbitration Association, and judgment on the award rendered by the arbitrator(s) shall be binding on the parties and may be entered in any court having jurisdiction. Regardless of any statute or law to the contrary, any claim or cause of action arising out of or related to your use of the Services or this Privacy Policy must be filed within one (1) year after such claim or cause of action arose or was reasonable discovered, whichever is later, or be forever barred. In the event of any Litigation, both parties expressly and irremovably consent to the exclusive venue and personal jurisdiction in New York County, New York. In the event of any Litigation arising from, related to or in connection with this Privacy Policy or the Services, the prevailing party thereof shall be entitled to recover its reasonable expenses, including (without limitation) attorneys. fees and the costs of arbitration. 

Any proceedings to resolve or litigate any Litigation in any forum will be conducted solely on an individual basis. You will not seek to have any Litigation heard as a class action, private attorney general action, or in any other proceeding in which either party acts or proposes to act in a representative capacity. 

## HOW TO CONTACT US

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information-handling practices, please contact us by email or postal mail as follows: 

Slimware Utilities Holdings, Inc.  
555 West 18th Street  
New York, NY 10011  
ATTN: Privacy  
Officer/Legal Dept.
